[
  {
    "question": "أفغانستان",
    "response": "كابول"
  },
  {
    "question": "ألبانيا",
    "response": "تيرانا"
  },
  {
    "question": "الجزائر",
    "response": "الجزائر"
  },
  {
    "question": "أندورا",
    "response": "أندورا لا فيلا"
  },
  {
    "question": "أنغولا",
    "response": "لواندا"
  },
  {
    "question": "الأرجنتين",
    "response": "بوينس آيرس"
  },
  {
    "question": "أرمينيا",
    "response": "يريفان"
  },
  {
    "question": "أستراليا",
    "response": "كانبيرا"
  },
  {
    "question": "النمسا",
    "response": "فيينا"
  },
  {
    "question": "أذربيجان",
    "response": "باكو"
  },
  {
    "question": "البحرين",
    "response": "المنامة"
  },
  {
    "question": "بنغلاديش",
    "response": "دكا"
  },
  {
    "question": "بلجيكا",
    "response": "بروكسل"
  },
  {
    "question": "البرازيل",
    "response": "برازيليا"
  },
  {
    "question": "بلغاريا",
    "response": "صوفيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "كندا",
    "response": "أوتاوا"
  },
  {
    "question": "الصين",
    "response": "بكين"
  },
  {
    "question": "كولومبيا",
    "response": "بوغوتا"
  },
  {
    "question": "كرواتيا",
    "response": "زغرب"
  },
  {
    "question": "كوبا",
    "response": "هافانا"
  },
  {
    "question": "قبرص",
    "response": "نيقوسيا"
  },
  {
    "question": "التشيك",
    "response": "براغ"
  },
  {
    "question": "الدنمارك",
    "response": "كوبنهاغن"
  },
  {
    "question": "مصر",
    "response": "القاهرة"
  },
  {
    "question": "فرنسا",
    "response": "باريس"
  },
  {
    "question": "ألمانيا",
    "response": "برلين"
  },
  {
    "question": "اليونان",
    "response": "أثينا"
  },
  {
    "question": "الهند",
    "response": "نيودلهي"
  },
  {
    "question": "إندونيسيا",
    "response": "جاكرتا"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيران",
    "response": "طهران"
  },
  {
    "question": "إيطاليا",
    "response": "روما"
  },
  {
    "question": "اليابان",
    "response": "طوكيو"
  },
  {
    "question": "الأردن",
    "response": "عمان"
  },
  {
    "question": "كازاخستان",
    "response": "أستانا"
  },
  {
    "question": "كينيا",
    "response": "نيروبي"
  },
  {
    "question": "كوريا الجنوبية",
    "response": "سول"
  },
  {
    "question": "الكويت",
    "response": "مدينة الكويت"
  },
  {
    "question": "لبنان",
    "response": "بيروت"
  },
  {
    "question": "ليبيا",
    "response": "طرابلس"
  },
  {
    "question": "المكسيك",
    "response": "مكسيكو سيتي"
  },
  {
    "question": "المغرب",
    "response": "الرباط"
  },
  {
    "question": "هولندا",
    "response": "أمستردام"
  },
  {
    "question": "نيجيريا",
    "response": "أبوجا"
  },
  {
    "question": "النرويج",
    "response": "أوسلو"
  },
  {
    "question": "عمان",
    "response": "مسقط"
  },
  {
    "question": "باكستان",
    "response": "إسلام أباد"
  },
  {
    "question": "فلسطين",
    "response": "القدس"
  },
  {
    "question": "الفلبين",
    "response": "مانيلا"
  },
  {
    "question": "بولندا",
    "response": "وارسو"
  },
  {
    "question": "البرتغال",
    "response": "لشبونة"
  },
  {
    "question": "قطر",
    "response": "الدوحة"
  },
  {
    "question": "رومانيا",
    "response": "بوخارست"
  },
  {
    "question": "روسيا",
    "response": "موسكو"
  },
  {
    "question": "السعودية",
    "response": "الرياض"
  },
  {
    "question": "السنغال",
    "response": "داكار"
  },
  {
    "question": "صربيا",
    "response": "بلغراد"
  },
  {
    "question": "سنغافورة",
    "response": "سنغافورة"
  },
  {
    "question": "سلوفاكيا",
    "response": "براتيسلافا"
  },
  {
    "question": "سلوفينيا",
    "response": "ليوبليانا"
  },
  {
    "question": "الصومال",
    "response": "مقديشو"
  },
  {
    "question": "جنوب أفريقيا",
    "response": "بريتوريا"
  },
  {
    "question": "إسبانيا",
    "response": "مدريد"
  },
  {
    "question": "السودان",
    "response": "الخرطوم"
  },
  {
    "question": "السويد",
    "response": "ستوكهولم"
  },
  {
    "question": "سويسرا",
    "response": "برن"
  },
  {
    "question": "سوريا",
    "response": "دمشق"
  },
  {
    "question": "تايوان",
    "response": "تايبيه"
  },
  {
    "question": "تنزانيا",
    "response": "دودوما"
  },
  {
    "question": "تايلاند",
    "response": "بانكوك"
  },
  {
    "question": "تونس",
    "response": "تونس"
  },
  {
    "question": "تركيا",
    "response": "أنقرة"
  },
  {
    "question": "أوكرانيا",
    "response": "كييف"
  },
  {
    "question": "الإمارات",
    "response": "أبوظبي"
  },
  {
    "question": "المملكة المتحدة",
    "response": "لندن"
  },
  {
    "question": "الولايات المتحدة",
    "response": "واشنطن"
  },
  {
    "question": "أوروغواي",
    "response": "مونتفيدو"
  },
  {
    "question": "فنزويلا",
    "response": "كاراكاس"
  },
  {
    "question": "فيتنام",
    "response": "هانوي"
  },
  {
    "question": "اليمن",
    "response": "صنعاء"
  }
]